

# HAKAN DEMIR JUNIOR DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a resourceful, result-oriented, fast learner and I am adaptable to new environments, with 6 years of experience in the telecommunications industry. Now, I would like to improve myself and by gaining knowledge and experience in software development within IT sector that I am constantly interested in and want to work in. Also, I have a residence and work permit n Estonia.

#### **CONTACT DETAIL**

- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hkn-demir/
- https://github.com/HknDmr
- hkn-demir@hotmail.com
- **\( +372 58140910**
- ♠ Tallinn/Estonia

## **TELECOMMUNICATION SKILLS**

- Tems Tools
- Genex Probe
- Actix
- Map Info
- Ms Office

## **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript (Learning)
- Bootstrap (Learning)
- Elementor
- JQuery
- Ms SQL
- MS Office

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Electra Telecommunication**

## **Drive Tests Managament** (Jan 2021 - Jun 2022)

- Drive Tests Management,
- · Log checking with MS SQL,
- ICT Measurement Management,
- Measurement Engineer (On Behalf Of Umlaut Company),
- Benchmark Measurements Management,
- · Benchmark Reporting,
- Install OS on computers and some devices

#### **Electra Telecommunication**

## Drive Tests Engineer (Jan 2020 - Jun 2021)

- Drive Test Engineer,
- Measurement Engineer (On Behalf Of Umlaut Company),
- Benchmark Measurement,
- RTU Device Control.
- Install OS on computers and some devices,
- Installing Drive Tests Tools and Devices

## **Noya International**

# Drive Tests Engineer&Reporting (Jan 2016 - Dec 2019)

- 2G-3G-4G Drive Tests And Reporting,
- Swap Tests Coordination and Planning DT Teams,
- Swap Tests Reports,
- Installing Drive Tests Tools and Devices

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

**Istanbul Aydin University** 



Biomedical Device Technology

Year of Graduation: 2012-2015

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



**Udemy** 

**SQL** Courses



**HackerRank** 

SQL Basic